http://www.skylineproducts.com/privacy-policy/

Latest News
Search for:
Designed to be bold. Engineered to last.
Contact Us
Support
Call Us: 1-866-961-4084
Skyline Products
Designed to be bold. Engineered to last.
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.skylineproducts.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.Information Collection, Use, and SharingSkyline Products, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will not share your information with any third party outside our organization except with necessary to fulfill your request (e.g. to ship an order or to process a specific information request). We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, Skyline Products news, surveys, trade events, other promotional opportunities, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. At any time, you can click the unsubscribe link included in promotional emails.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individualsdue to the following reasons:To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Service issued.We want to inform that some third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. We also employ security measures for data stored offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, sales, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesWe use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Children’s PrivacyOur Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at 866-961-4084 or partners@skylineproducts.com.
Back to top
Explore Our Price Signs
Our Transportation Projects
Divisions Price Signs
Transportation
Fuel Pricing Software
About
About Skyline Products
© 2016 SKYLINE PRODUCTS.ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
Search:
